okay it's about 11 o'clock
and there's another interesting
phenomenon here
the joe sell might turn it on
over there this battery charger
throws out about 12 volts 8 amps
charges this joe cell and the battery
charger is off right now but if you can
see this
this light is on let me try this i'm
gonna
turn it on
and watch this light okay
here goes the joe show
i'm going to turn it off there we go
turning it off over here once you watch
the light
it's off but the light
is still on let's turn off my
other fluorescent light here
figure that one out joe shell is off
battery chargers off light still
on
turn it on one more time
here's the cell
this is our light
we're off
the led is still on
if i turn the battery charger on it does
get brighter
here we go again ready on
notice the cell
i'm just going to let it run for a few
seconds and off
interesting
the joe cell chronicles